I had a gentleman who came six plus months ago.
I'll take it some months earlier, came out here,
took time away from the business,
and finally gets his chance to have a question.
And he says, hey, Alex, can you go through
the Closer framework?
And I said, before I answer the question,
can you tell me what Closer rate is?
And he says, 40%.
So you went through all of that
to have this one opportunity to have an answer
that in no way will change your business.
A lot of times, us as entrepreneurs,
we will focus on the thing that we enjoy the most
rather than the thing that the business needs the most.
And typically the thing the business needs the most
is not the thing that you're the best at.
A lot of times, art efficiencies
translate into the business efficiencies.
And you can be unbalanced as an entrepreneur,
but the business can't be.
You will always be constrained
by whatever the weak link is in the business,
and that's fundamentally the whole point
of the theory of constraints.